These four of us have arrived at the Hoshino Resort Hotel.
Now please open the door.
Yu-chan has always dreamed of staying here.
It's been a dream of hers for a long time.
You've always wanted to stay at Hoshino Resort.
Finally, we're at our dream hotel.
Come in.
Let's go in.
Wow! It's so cute!
It's amazing.
Yuuchan.
So cute!
Amazing.
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute.
We should all live here.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
It's so much fun.
A hundred times better than I imagined.
There's a mysterious space.
What is it?
Oh!
Oh, my God!
It's real!
It's beautiful!
It's so beautiful!
Let's have fun!
We'll have a rock-paper-scissors-scissors contest to see which bed is best!
You want to pick from the rock-paper-scissors tournament?
Let's do it! Ready!Here we go! Ready!
First, goo!
No, no, no!
First, goo! Rock, paper, scissors!
You're playing rock-paper-scissors-paper!
Ui! Put it in, put it in, put it in.
Okay, in the back is Mr. Otsuka and Mr. Matoba, and in the front is me and Juuna. Thank you very much.
You're too kind. You're too kind.
You shouldn't do that. You'll catch a cold.
Joona, you're fast asleep.
Oh, Otsuka-san, Otsuka-san, Otsuka-san
This is how we do it. This room. That's all.
It was bed rock-paper-scissors-scissors, wasn't it? Bye bye.
Wow!
It's amazing!
No, I'll have to get some pasta.
Don't burn the pasta, too.
Oh, wow. That's great.
We don't have a situation.
Where are we?
We're already going back there.
What's that?
It's a Dyson dryer.
Oh, shit!
Help me.
The bathroom is clean.
Good morning.
I'm here in Okinawa.
You know that bonfire in front of the lobby at night?
Oh, here it is.
I feel like everything is already here.
It's burning.
I could spend the whole day here.
We could spend the whole day here, or if you want, we could spend the whole day at the hotel.
We can go anywhere.
I can go anywhere.I can go, really.
I just got in the pool.
It was cold.
I thought I was swimming with my Ukiyoe like this,
I saw her smiling.
It was so cute, like a fish.
Cheeser!
You look like a cheeser!
I'm having fun.
A party that feels like a resort.
Beboi, this is seriously the best.
I thought it was us. We're the only group that made it here.
We're the only ones who could've won.
Let's Instagram it! I really want to know about it!
We're in the Lux Suite. What are you, a genius?
Big windows. Big windows.
There's more beds than there are people in this room. Yeah, and each person can have two beds.
I think I'll just jump in one at a time. Yay!
We're going to shoot after this. We're going to do our best.
Please subscribe to our channel.
He's so cute!
It's so cute!
What do you think of my grandchildren?
He's so cute!
He's so cute.
I never thought my grandson would be so popular in his life.
It's a great cure.
I've been able to take good care of my parents.
This is going to work?
Isn't this nice?
So good!
Ouch!
Akari, put half the noodles in this.
I'll take care of it.
Keep them in the soup.
I'll let them swim in the soup.I'll let it swim in the broth.
I'll cut the juice from this stewed cubes.
Finished.
What do you think?
I can't believe we can eat such melt-in-your-mouth meat from frozen!
Is it true?
It's nothing but delicious!
It's best to eat this thick rasagyu with noodles
It's the best to eat it with noodles in a broth that has a gentle broth.
Delicious!
There's Jim!
We did it!
I'm so happy!
Wow, I didn't know they had a gym!
I've never been to a hotel this far from here that has a gym with a system like this.
I've never seen such a well-equipped gym in a hotel this far away.
I've never seen one before.
That's great.
You know what they have here?
There's a yoga map.
It's easy to do.
There's an abdominal brawl.
I can do this.
I can run.
Oh, my God.
You want to run?
I think I'll run.
There's a safety app.
What's that? Is there such a thing?
Yeah, there is.
It's a lifeline.
Start out slow.
And this guy, he uses a peeler. Slowly.
Oh, my God.
Oh, wow.
Uh, uh, uh, and then slowly...Uh, yeah, so gradually.
Like a gradual run.
Eh, that's cool.
Let's take a little licking shot.
That's cool.
I go to the gym all the time.
Like this.
I'm always going to the gym.
I can travel and stuff.
I can't go to the gym
I feel like I'm going to go to the gym
I'm really ready to go to the session.
For Marina
Sparkling and shining.
You said you have a gym.
My favorite feeling
Wow, muscle is power.
And you're so beautiful.
You're so beautiful.
Amazing.
Chan-chan...
I feel like I can't run.
After all
It's super simple.
Can I go higher?
That's great.
It's kind of funny.
What's with the dog? He's running.
What is it?
What do you think?
It's great.
It's Apple.
Oh, my God.
Oh, wow!
Wow.
I worked hard for one job.I worked hard for one job.
Fun! Great!
Hey, it's nice!
It was a hotel for marinas.
Great!
It's so sweet!
Babe!